[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Taste of Love]
[طعم الحب]
[Episode 17]
[الحلقة 17]
[King of Jealousy in Asia]
[ملك الغيرة في آسيا]
Didn't I ask you
ألم أسألك
to look for Jing Lian's information?
للبحث عن معلومات جينغ ليان؟
Isn't that it?
أليس هذا كل شيء؟
But this is obviously Chubby Su!
لكن من الواضح أن هذا هو Chubby Su!
This is Jing Lian.
هذا جينغ ليان.
What's she doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
She is the leader of
هي قائدة
a new girl group.
مجموعة فتيات جديدة.
And she is recording
وهي تقوم بالتسجيل
a new variety show.
عرض متنوع جديد.
Why is she dressed like this?
لماذا ترتدي مثل هذا؟
In order to show herself more
لكي تظهر نفسها أكثر
in front of the camera.
أمام الكاميرا.
As a rookie,
بصفتك مبتدئًا ،
she has to do something different
عليها أن تفعل شيئًا مختلفًا
to hold the audience's attention,
لجذب انتباه الجمهور ،
right?
يمين؟
It seems that she can do anything to get famous.
يبدو أنها تستطيع فعل أي شيء لتصبح مشهورة.
You just came in time.
لقد أتيت للتو في الوقت المناسب.
I need your advice.
أحتاج نصيحتك.
I have something
لدي شيئ ما
to discuss with you.
لمناقشته معك.
You go first.
اذهب أولا.
What time are you leaving
في أي وقت ستغادر
for the promotion of
للترويج لـ
Love and Espionage tomorrow?
الحب والتجسس غدا؟
I want to stagger the time with you.
أريد أن أقوم بترتيب الوقت معك.
Why?
لماذا؟
If we arrive at the same
إذا وصلنا إلى نفس الشيء
time,
وقت،
the reporters may guess that
قد يخمن الصحفيون ذلك
we are together.
نحن سوية.
The supporting actress
الممثلة الداعمة
fell in love with the producer
وقعت في حب المنتج
when the TV play starts to broadcast.
عندما يبدأ البث التلفزيوني.
That would create a bad impression
من شأنه أن يخلق انطباعًا سيئًا
and will harm the publicity of this TV play.
وسيضر بالدعاية لهذه المسرحية التلفزيونية.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
I understand.
أفهم.
Actually, I thought about it long ago,
في الواقع ، فكرت في الأمر منذ فترة طويلة ،
but I didn't have time to tell you.
لكن لم يكن لدي الوقت لأخبرك.
When are you going?
متى ستذهب؟
I won't attend it.
لن أحضرها.
Won't you attend
لن تحضر
such an important event?
مثل هذا الحدث المهم؟
Time Entertainment
وقت الترفيه
has invested in a lot of TV plays.
استثمر في الكثير من المسرحيات التلفزيونية.
I have no time to
ليس لدي وقت ل
take part in all of them.
المشاركة في كل منهم.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
After all, you are the boss.
بعد كل شيء ، أنت الرئيس.
All right, I have nothing else to say.
حسنًا ، ليس لدي أي شيء آخر أقوله.
Have a good rest.
لديها راحة جيدة.
I'm going to get ready.
انا ذاهب للاستعداد.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Boss,
رئيس،
I'll pick you up
أنا سأقلك
at 9 a.m. tomorrow, okay?
الساعة 9 صباحًا غدًا ، حسنًا؟
I don't need that.
لا أحتاج ذلك.
Have I ever participated
هل سبق لي أن شاركت
in such activities?
في مثل هذه الأنشطة؟
But isn't Love and Espionage
لكن ليس الحب والتجسس
a special one?
خاص؟
Aren't I busy enough
ألست مشغول بما فيه الكفاية
dealing with the work in the company?
التعامل مع العمل في الشركة؟
I'll stay in the company tomorrow.
سأبقى في الشركة غدا.
I'm not going anywhere.
لن أذهب إلى أي مكان.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
[Love and Espionage]
[الحب والتجسس]
This is Chayan TV.
هذا تلفزيون Chayan.
I'm the host, Tao.
أنا المضيف ، تاو.
Now, we are at the scene
الآن ، نحن في مكان الحادث
of the Love and Espionage launch event
من حفل إطلاق الحب والتجسس
and waiting for the leading roles to show up.
وانتظار ظهور الأدوار القيادية.
I will continue to report to you.
سأستمر في إبلاغك.
Here they are!
ها هم!
-The car is here! -The car is here!
-السيارة هنا!  -السيارة هنا!
Time Entertainment gets a lot of attention.
تحظى Time Entertainment بالكثير من الاهتمام.
-So beautiful! -So beautiful!
-جميل جدا!  -جميل جدا!
Mengmeng, look over here.
Mengmeng ، انظر هنا.
Miss Yu, can you look here?
آنسة يو ، هل يمكنك أن تنظر هنا؟
-Yes. -You're so beautiful!
-نعم.  -ًأنت جميلة جدا!
Okay. Thank you.
تمام.  شكرًا لك.
So beautiful!
جميل جدا!
-So beautiful! -So beautiful!
-جميل جدا!  -جميل جدا!
Mengmeng, look here!
Mengmeng ، انظر هنا!
Mengmeng, here!
Mengmeng ، هنا!
Look here!
انظر هنا!
They're so matching!
إنهم متطابقون للغاية!
Thank you to all the media
شكرا لجميع وسائل الإعلام
for attending
للحضور
our launch event today.
حدث الإطلاق اليوم.
Please support
الرجاء الدعم
the TV play
تشغيل التلفزيون
I starred in.
لقد تألقت في.
-Okay. -Okay.
-تمام.  -تمام.
Miss Tang,
ملكة جمال تانغ ،
ever since Time Entertainment
منذ وقت الترفيه
invested in Love and Espionage,
استثمرت في الحب والتجسس ،
so to speak,
إذا جاز التعبير،
you went straight from a guest extra
ذهبت مباشرة من ضيف إضافي
to the supporting actress.
للممثلة الداعمة.
What's the relationship between you
ما هي العلاقة بينكما
and Times Entertainment?
وتايمز انترتينمنت؟
Tangsu, please tell us.
تانغسو ، من فضلك قل لنا.
We really want to know.
نحن حقا نريد أن نعرف.
Tell us.
أخبرنا.
Tell us something!
اخبرنا شيئا!
Actually...
في الحقيقة...
Here's the thing.
هنا الحاجة.
Everyone recognized
اعترف الجميع
Tang Su's acting skills
مهارات التمثيل تانغ سو
during this filming.
خلال هذا التصوير.
That's why Time Entertainment
لهذا السبب تايم إنترتينمنت
gave her this chance.
أعطاها هذه الفرصة.
So I request all of you
لذلك أطلب منكم جميعًا
don't doubt her randomly,
لا تشك بها بشكل عشوائي ،
okay?
تمام؟
So it is.
اذا هي كذلك.
Miss Tang,
ملكة جمال تانغ ،
I saw you and Jing Lian
رأيتك أنت وجينغ ليان
getting along well.
تتأقلم جيدا.
Can you talk about your collaboration at this time?
هل يمكنك التحدث عن تعاونك في هذا الوقت؟
How do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
I think Jing Lian
أعتقد جينغ ليان
is a very professional actor.
هو ممثل محترف للغاية.
We had a great time
لقد قضينا وقتا رائعا
working together.
العمل سويا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Can you two come closer?
هل تستطيعان الاقتراب؟
Please come closer.
من فضلك اقترب.
So sweet!
حلوة جدا!
Can you come closer?
هل يمكنك الاقتراب؟
-Thank you. -Thank you.
-شكرًا لك.  -شكرًا لك.
You're like a couple.
أنتما مثل الزوجين.
So sweet.
حلوة جدا.
So sour.
تعكر جدا.
Orange.
البرتقالي.
This orange is sour.
هذا البرتقال حامض.
Don't be weird.
لا تكن غريبا.
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Su!
هم!
Come here quickly! Look!
تعال الي هنا بسرعة!  ينظر!
Breaking news!
أخبار عاجلة!
Your new TV play became a trending topic
أصبحت مسرحية التلفزيون الجديدة موضوعًا شائعًا
as soon as it started broadcasting!
بمجرد أن بدأ البث!
Look.
ينظر.
They even gave
حتى أنهم أعطوا
a name to the combination of you two,
اسم للجمع بينكما ،
"Tang Jing Couple".
"زوجان تانغ جينغ".
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why do you look so tired?
لماذا تبدو متعبا جدا؟
I'm really tired.
أنا حقا متعب.
I keep working for the events of
أواصل العمل من أجل أحداث
Love and Espionage these days.
الحب والتجسس هذه الايام.
After the end of the event today,
بعد انتهاء حدث اليوم ،
Luo Shi told me to come over and talked to me.
أخبرني لوه أن آتي وتحدث معي.
He told me...
قال لي...
I should keep a low-key with my relationship status
يجب أن أحافظ على مستوى منخفض من حالة علاقتي
and keep a single image.
واحتفظ بصورة واحدة.
I should also keep a high-key to propagandize my couple
يجب أن أحافظ أيضًا على مفتاح عالي للدعاية لزوجي
to get more attentions.
لجذب المزيد من الانتباه.
Both high key and low key?
كلاً من المفتاح العالي والمفتاح المنخفض؟
Is he playing a musical instrument?
هل يعزف على آلة موسيقية؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It's not my first day to be an artist.
إنه ليس أول يوم لي أن أصبح فنانًا.
I know what to do.
أنا أعرف ما يجب القيام به.
But...
لكن...
If I keep my relationship a secret,
إذا أبقيت علاقتي سرية ،
I may hurt him.
قد أؤذيه.
In my opinion,
في رأيي،
he is also
وهو أيضا
working in the entertainment industry.
العمل في صناعة الترفيه.
He will understand you.
سوف يفهمك.
Don't think too much.
لا تفكر كثيرا.
Have a good rest.
لديها راحة جيدة.
I'll talk to him.
سوف اتحدث معه.
Okay.
تمام.
Why do you stay up so late?
لماذا تسهر حتى وقت متأخر؟
Are you reading?
هل انت تقرأ؟
You stay up late too.
أنت تبقى مستيقظا لوقت متأخر أيضا.
What a full day, huh?
يا له من يوم كامل ، هاه؟
You're the trending topic now.
أنت الموضوع الرائج الآن.
So jealous.
غيور جدا.
I think someone is angry.
أعتقد أن شخصًا ما غاضب.
How could I be that childish?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون طفولية؟
So you're not angry.
لذلك أنت لست غاضبًا.
Fine.
بخير.
I wanted to make it up to you.
أردت أن أعوضها لك.
How?
كيف؟
Go on a date and watch a movie.
اذهب في موعد وشاهد فيلمًا.
Sure!
بالتأكيد!
The one in front.
واحد في المقدمة.
Can you take off your hat?
هل يمكنك خلع قبعتك؟
Aren't you Tang... Tang Su?
ألست تانغ ... تانغ سو؟
-Tangsu? -Tangsu?
-تانغسو؟  -تانغسو؟
That's Tang Su.
هذا تانغ سو.
She left!
لقد غادرت!
Who is that man?
من هذا الرجل؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Tang Su!
تانغ سو!
Aren't we suitable for dating?
ألسنا مناسبين للمواعدة؟
Did you go to a marathon?
هل ذهبت الى ماراثون؟
-It's so hard. -It's so hard.
-انه صعب جدا.  -انه صعب جدا.
So that's what happened.
هذا ما حدث.
However,
لكن،
as public characters,
كشخصيات عامة ،
we will definitely sacrifice
سوف نضحي بالتأكيد
lots of personal time.
الكثير من الوقت الشخصي.
Look at Ye and me.
انظروا لي وأنا.
We haven't seen each other
لم نر بعضنا البعض
for a long time.
لفترة طويلة.
How long is it?
كم طوله؟
It's been more than 10 hours.
لقد مرت أكثر من 10 ساعات.
I'm speechless.
أنا عاجز عن الكلام.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
Don't listen to the words
لا تستمع للكلمات
Luo Shi told you.
قال لك لوه شي.
Who decided artists
من قرر الفنانين
can't date?
لا تستطيع المواعدة؟
The problem is,
المشكلة هي،
I'm an obscure artist
أنا فنان غامض
who just made a comeback,
الذي عاد للتو ،
but now I'm dating a boss of the entertainment industry.
لكنني الآن أواعد رئيسًا في صناعة الترفيه.
What will others think about me?
ماذا سيفكر الآخرون عني؟
They may think that
قد يعتقدون ذلك
I'm doing this for rapid ascent.
أنا أفعل هذا من أجل الصعود السريع.
Then it'd be useless no matter how hard I try.
ثم سيكون عديم الفائدة بغض النظر عن مدى صعوبة المحاولة.
Besides, I don't want other people
علاوة على ذلك ، لا أريد أشخاصًا آخرين
to misunderstand Huangfu Jue.
لإساءة فهم Huangfu Jue.
Have you asked Huangfu Jue about his will?
هل سألت Huangfu Jue عن إرادته؟
Does he want to hide it too?
هل يريد إخفاءها أيضًا؟
I have yet to ask him.
لم أسأله بعد.
But he didn't even attend
لكنه لم يحضر حتى
the launch event.
حدث الإطلاق.
He probably doesn't care about it.
ربما لا يهتم بذلك.
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
I think
أظن
he's becoming more jealous than before.
لقد أصبح أكثر غيرة من ذي قبل.
But nothing happened
و لكن لم يحدث شىء
between Jing Lian and me.
بيني وبين جينغ ليان.
Of course I know.
بالطبع أنا أعلم.
But
لكن
as your boyfriend,
كصديقك ،
when he sees the news online,
عندما يرى الأخبار على الإنترنت ،
I'm sure he will
أنا متأكد من أنه سيفعل
feel uncomfortable.
تشعر بعدم الارتياح.
Then what should I do?
إذن ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
Tang Su and Jing Lian are like a sweet couple.
تانغ سو وجينغ ليان مثل زوجين حلوين.
I follow their TV play every day
أتابع لعبهم التلفزيوني كل يوم
just to see them.
فقط لرؤيتهم.
I'm praying that they can be a real couple one day.
أنا أدعو الله أن يكونا زوجين حقيقيين يومًا ما.
Tang Jing Couple is the sweetest in the world!
تانغ جينغ زوجان هو أحلى في العالم!
There are so many news about my couple.
هناك الكثير من الأخبار عن زوجي.
If this continues,
إذا استمر هذا ،
Huangfu Jue will go crazy.
سوف يجن هوانغفو جو.
Tang Su,
تانغ سو ،
you will go viral soon.
سوف تنتشر قريبًا.
So it would be best if you
لذلك سيكون من الأفضل إذا كنت
seize this opportunity.
اغتنم هذه الفرصة.
I don't need these hot topics
لست بحاجة إلى هذه المواضيع الساخنة
to hype myself.
للدعاية لنفسي.
I want to prove my ability with my works.
أريد إثبات قدرتي من خلال أعمالي.
Can you be more professional?
هل يمكنك أن تكون أكثر احترافا؟
I can be professional.
يمكنني أن أكون محترفًا.
But I hope
ولكن أتمنى
you can stop hyping me.
يمكنك التوقف عن المبالغة بي.
I don't want to cooperate with it anymore.
لا أريد التعاون معها بعد الآن.
I know. I know.
أنا أعرف.  أنا أعرف.
You are just tired.
أنت فقط متعب.
You know?
أنت تعرف؟
Go back and have a good rest.
ارجع واستمتع براحة جيدة.
Chubby Su!
سو السمين!
What's wrong with you? It's so early!
ما مشكلتك؟  الوقت مبكر جدا!
I want to talk to Chubby Su.
أريد التحدث إلى تشابي سو.
Don't you know that she went out for filming
الا تعلم انها خرجت للتصوير
early this morning?
باكرا هذا الصباح؟
Filming?
التصوير؟
Did she get a new TV play?
هل حصلت على مسرحية تلفزيونية جديدة؟
I think
أظن
you don't care about
لا يهمك
Su's schedule at all.
جدول سو على الإطلاق.
She's filming an extra story
إنها تصور قصة إضافية
for Love and Espionage.
من أجل الحب والتجسس.
Stop disturbing me.
توقف عن إزعاجي.
Bye.
الوداع.
So, she is with Jing Lian again.
لذا ، فهي مع جينغ ليان مرة أخرى.
When you make contact with the agents,
عندما تتواصل مع الوكلاء ،
never ask questions that
لا تطرح الأسئلة التي
don't concern you.
لا تقلقك.
Don't interfere in matters
لا تتدخل في الأمور
that don't concern you.
هذا لا يهمك.
I know, Mengyao.
أعرف يا مينجياو.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
We will survive.
سننجو.
Okay, cut. It's okay.
حسنًا ، قص.  لا بأس.
Thank you for your hard work.
شكرا لعملكم الشاق.
Let's go to eat lunch.
دعنا نذهب لتناول الغداء.
-Okay. -Thank you, Director.
-تمام.  -شكرا لك أيها المدير.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
-No need. -I…
-لا حاجة.  -أنا…
Wait, let me do it.
انتظر ، دعني أفعل ذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
The chicken is very delicious.
الدجاج لذيذ جدا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I don't like it.
أنا لا أحب ذلك.
Did I do something
هل فعلت شيء ما
that made you unhappy?
الذي جعلك غير سعيد؟
We're just colleagues.
نحن مجرد زملاء.
You don't have to be so attentive.
ليس عليك أن تكون منتبهًا جدًا.
And I don't want to
وأنا لا أريد ذلك
continue our business couple anymore.
أكمل الزوجين في العمل لدينا بعد الآن.
But our company...
لكن شركتنا ...
I know the company
أعرف الشركة
gave you instructions.
أعطاك التعليمات.
You may think
ربما تفكر
this is your career plan.
هذه هي خطتك المهنية.
But I think,
لكنني أعتقد،
if you want to go far,
إذا كنت تريد أن تذهب بعيدا ،
you must rely on your professional ability
يجب أن تعتمد على قدرتك المهنية
instead of
بدلاً من
those fake things.
تلك الأشياء المزيفة.
Besides...
بجانب...
It's okay. Let's eat.
لا بأس.  لنأكل.
Why are you so serious?
لماذا انت جاد جدا
I don't care about the tactics
لا أهتم بالتكتيكات
or instructions.
أو التعليمات.
I just want to
أريد فقط
talk to you about old times.
أتحدث إليكم عن العصور القديمة.
Old times?
الأيام الخوالي؟
When you fell
عندما وقعت
on the stage,
على المسرح،
it's me who watched you from behind.
أنا من راقبك من الخلف.
So,
لذا،
you were that person who
كنت ذلك الشخص الذي
watched me behind the scenes!
راقبني من وراء الكواليس!
Yes, it's me.
نعم هذا انا.
I was so embarrassed.
انا كنت محرجا كثيرا.
Don't worry, Senior.
لا تقلق يا كبير.
I won't laugh at you
لن أضحك عليك
even if everyone laughs at you.
حتى لو ضحك الجميع عليك.
Okay, you're sincere. I believe you.
حسنًا ، أنت مخلص.  واعتقد انكم.
Really!
حقًا!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I misunderstood you.
لقد أسأت فهمك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Miss Tang.
ملكة جمال تانغ.
Miss Tang,
ملكة جمال تانغ ،
could you please come here?
هل يمكنك القدوم إلى هنا من فضلك
I'll leave first.
سأغادر أولا.
Okay. Cheer up!
تمام.  ابتهج!
Mr. Huangfu?
السيد هوانغفو؟
You should know who I am.
يجب أن تعرف من أنا.
Of course I do.
بالطبع افعل.
You are the investor of this play.
أنت المستثمر في هذه المسرحية.
Speaking of which,
بالحديث عن هذا الموضوع،
I should thank you.
يجب أن أشكرك.
Thanks to your investment,
شكرا لاستثمارك ،
I can have the chance
يمكنني الحصول على الفرصة
to be with Tang Su.
أن أكون مع تانغ سو.
Think about it carefully.
فكر في الأمر بعناية.
OK.
نعم.
You should thank me a lot.
يجب أن تشكرني كثيرا.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Huangfu Jue?
هوانغفو جو؟
Where are you going, Huangfu Jue?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب ، هوانغفو جو؟
Huangfu Jue!
هوانغفو جو!
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
You just came here.
لقد أتيت للتو إلى هنا.
I think you don't want me to come.
أعتقد أنك لا تريدني أن آتي.
Why are you so angry?
لماذا انت غاضب جدا؟
I'm your
انا لك
real boyfriend,
صديقها الحقيقي ،
but I don't even have the right to make it public.
لكن ليس لدي حتى الحق في نشرها على الملأ.
Everyone is saying
الجميع يقول
you and another man
أنت ورجل آخر
are a matching couple.
هما زوجان متطابقان.
Everyone is saying
الجميع يقول
how sweet and happy you are.
كم انت لطيف وسعيد.
How can I not be angry?
كيف لا اغضب؟
Why can't you understand?
لماذا لا تفهم؟
This is just my job.
هذا هو عملي فقط.
I understand.
أفهم.
But it doesn't mean I can accept it.
لكن هذا لا يعني أنه يمكنني قبولها.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I thought you didn't mind.
اعتقدت أنك لا تمانع.
How could I not mind?
كيف لا أمانع؟
I thought
اعتقدت
you were acting.
كنت تتصرف.
If I hadn't seen it with my own eyes,
إذا لم أره بأم عيني ،
I wouldn't have known
لم أكن لأعرف
you were so close.
كنت قريبا جدا.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How could I not mind?
كيف لا أمانع؟
It's not like that.
إنه ليس كذلك.
He's just...
انه فقط...
I don't care who he is.
لا يهمني من هو.
He is not important to me.
إنه ليس مهمًا بالنسبة لي.
What matters is you.
ما يهم هو أنت.
I know you're avoiding suspicion.
أعلم أنك تتجنب الشك.
If it weren't for you,
إذا لم تكن لك ،
I would have told the whole world
كنت سأخبر العالم كله
you are my girlfriend.
انت حبيبتي.
I know you work so hard
أنا أعلم أنك تعمل بجد
to become a better artist.
لتصبح فنانًا أفضل.
I know
أنا أعرف
you refused my help
رفضت مساعدتي
because you don't want others to look down on you.
لأنك لا تريد أن ينظر إليك الآخرون باستخفاف.
But I don't care
لكني لا أهتم
what others think.
ما يعتقده الآخرون.
I only care about your feelings.
أنا فقط أهتم بمشاعرك.
As long as you
طالما انك
accept our relationship,
قبول علاقتنا ،
I'll respect your decision
سأحترم قرارك
whether you want to make it public.
ما إذا كنت تريد جعلها عامة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
I suddenly found that
وجدت ذلك فجأة
to wait for the so-called
لانتظار ما يسمى ب
"a suitable opportunity"
"فرصة مناسبة"
is a waste of time.
هو مضيعة للوقت.
Most importantly,
الاكثر اهمية،
we need to cherish
نحن بحاجة للاعتزاز
what we have now.
ما لدينا الآن.
Huangfu Jue,
هوانغفو جو ،
I'm going to
انا ذاهب الى
announce to the world that
أعلن للعالم أن
you are mine.
أنت لى.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
I want to announce something.
اريد ان اعلن شيئا.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I will no longer be alone.
لن أكون وحدي بعد الآن.
I have him
لدي
by my side.
بجانبي.
-Bravo! -Bravo!
-ولد جيد!  -ولد جيد!
Bravo!
أحسنت!